bestinclass.com 2008-07-26

# BestInClass.com: Privacy Policy

In operating the bestinclass.com web site (“Service”), BestInClass.com, Inc., (“Company”), adheres to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * when it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * if bestinclass.com or BestInClass.com, Inc. is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, the Company will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Information Gathering and Usage

  * When you register for the Service we ask for information such as your email address, username, age, and password.
  * We gather statistical information about user activity within our Service.
  * Users may choose to enter information such as product recommendations and comments.

The Company uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Service. We use cookies to record current session information, to remember login information if requested, to save user preferences, and to gather usage metrics.

## Disclosure

The Company may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

## Changes

The Company may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to BestInClass.com, Inc. at: 167 S. San Antonio Rd., Los Altos, CA 94022 USA
